var mediumLevel = [{
    "question": "What’s the default cluster size in the NTFS file system under Windows?",
    "choices": ["2 KB", "4 KB", "16 KB", "256 KB"],
    "correct": "4 KB"
}, {
    "question": "What’s the key combination to bring up the task manager directly in Win 7/ Vista?",
    "choices": ["Ctrl+alt+del", "Ctrl+shift+esc", "Ctrl+f1", "Alt+Shift"],
    "correct": "Ctrl+shift+esc"
}, {
    "question": "What is the slowest type of memory?",
    "choices": ["RAM", "SWAP FILE", "ROM", "SSD"],
    "correct": "SWAP FILE"
}, {
    "question": "Which commonly used in programming symbol is usually missing on most keyboards?",
    "choices": ["Pipe", "Asterix", "Tilde", "Percentage"],
    "correct": "Pipe"
}, {
    "question": "For a long time advancement in microprocessor technologies is marked not by increasing frequency" +
    " but by decreasing manufacturing process, which leads to improved power efficiency and architecture." +
    " What is the latest by Intel (mass production)?",
    "choices": ["32nm", "22nm", "14nm", "10nm"],
    "correct": "14nm"
}, {
    "question": "We already have „Acne for dummies” and „Raising cattle for dummies”, but which is the first book of the series?",
    "choices": ["Windows for Dummies", "Macintosh for Dummies", "Dos for Dummies", "C++ for Dummies"],
    "correct": "Dos for Dummies"

}, {
    "question": "Which of the below is one of the most recent programming languages?",
    "choices": ["Swift", "Groovy", "Windows Power Shell", "Delphi"],
    "correct": "Swift"

}, {
    "question": "In Unix-based OS it is called terminal, how is it called in Windows?",
    "choices": ["Port", "Debugger", "Control Panel", "CMD"],
    "correct": "CMD"

}, {
    "question": "In RGB system red is 255, 0, 0. In CMYK it is 0, 100, 100, 0, how about HTML notation?",
    "choices": ["0.0.0", "ff0000", "ffffff", "009900"],
    "correct": "ff0000"

}, {
    "question": "What did retina display initially mean when the term was first marketed by Apple?",
    "choices": ["Higher pixel count", "Higher pixel density", "Higher contrast and brightness", "Better viewing angles"],
    "correct": "Higher pixel count"
}];

quiz(mediumLevel);